The secret has traveled through centuries to reach you
The Secret is a documentary film directed by Drew Heriot.
Interviews with leading authors, philosophers and scientists, with
an in-depth discussion of the Law of Attraction.
The audience is shown how they can learn and use
'The Secret' in their everyday lives.
Self - Philosopher, played by Bob Proctor.
Self - Metaphysician, played by Joe Vitale.
Self - Entrepreneur, played by John Assaraf.
Self - Financial Strategist, played by Loral Langemeier.
Self - Feng Shui Consultant, played by Marie Diamond.
Self - Visionary, played by Michael Bernard Beckwith.
The Secret is a 2006 Australian-American spirituality pseudo-documentary consisting of a series of interviews designed to demonstrate the New Thought "law of attraction" - the belief that
everything one wants or needs can be satisfied by believing in an outcome, repeatedly thinking about it, and maintaining positive emotional states to "attract" the desired outcome.
The film and the subsequent publication of the book of the same name attracted interest
from media figures such as Oprah Winfrey, Ellen DeGeneres and Larry King.